<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bakeys Fitness</string>
    <string name="vid_fintess_dr_title">Types of training</string>
    <string name="vid_fintess_single_title">Type of training</string>
    <string name="vostok_praktik_title">Eastern practices</string>
    <string name="vostok_praktik_desc">All types of fitness training are aimed at specific tasks (stretching, building muscle mass, losing weight or strengthening the heart), include different types of loads (power, aerobic, combined) and involve certain body systems. Fitness programs that have similar characteristics are conventionally grouped into trends. In particular, these are oriental practices, classes with a dance bias, power or cardio workouts, mixed techniques and complexes that are more focused on stretching. In order to choose a suitable program for physical activity, it is better to get to know each type in more detail.</string>
    <string name="yoga_title">Yoga</string>
    <string name="yoga_desc">One of the most sought-after styles of modern fitness, with many subspecies, schools, and currents. It is based on traditional ancient Indian practices. Regardless of the direction, the workout is a combination of physical and spiritual techniques aimed at the all-round development of the body. During the class slowly perform static poses, in which you have to stay for some time. Particular attention is paid to proper breathing. Asanas relieve pain in the spine and joints, tone up the muscles of the body and have a generally beneficial effect on all body systems. Classes improve your psycho-emotional state and effectively fight stress, depression and insomnia. Yoga is available to people of all levels of fitness and is especially suitable for those who are not ready for intense exertion and vigorous athletic movement. Asanas can be practiced at all ages and weights.</string>
    <string name="taizi_title">Tai Chi</string>
    <string name="taizi_desc">The style is based on a martial art (a type of Wushu) devised by Chinese monks who observed animal behavior. As a consequence, the technique involves measured, gradual, flowing techniques and gestures slowly flowing into each other. The practices involve proper breathing, proper mental attitude and concentration. They as well as yoga are aimed at simultaneous physical and spiritual development. During the classes they often use weights and additional equipment, but this does not prevent them from recommending the technique to elderly people and those who have no physical training at all. Such exercises restores joint mobility, strengthens the heart and blood vessels, improves blood circulation and teaches how to maintain mental balance. Tai chi exercises relieve muscular and nervous tension, improve the mind, and give a restful sleep.</string>
    <string name="pilates_title">Pilates</string>
    <string name="pilates_desc">Developed from tai chi and yoga, the Pilates system includes small-amplitude dynamic movements designed to work (stretch and strengthen) every muscle in the body. There is also a clear interaction of exercises with the brain, but unlike some Eastern practices, there is no statics or \"yogic\" breathing. Regular performance of slow techniques makes muscles strong, aligns posture and helps with weight loss. Fans of Pilates say that you can practice this type of fitness in the gym as well as at home. And at any age and without a high level of fitness. But experts in the field and experienced coaches La Salute warn that, despite the safety of Pilates, exercises should begin under the control of an instructor. This will eliminate the possibility of injury and will maximize the development of elasticity of ligaments, joint flexibility, strength and endurance.</string>
    <string name="dance_aero_title">Aerobics</string>
    <string name="dance_aero_desc">The purpose of such workouts is to strengthen the muscle groups of the whole body, to lose weight and to relieve stress. Various styles are used in classes, such as hip-hop, funk, oriental and many others. And some dance programs have already transformed into a separate type with its own varieties. For example, zumba, whose training takes place in a fiery latin and includes movements of popular dances such as samba, mambo, flamenco and salsa.</string>
    <string name="pole_title">Pole Dance</string>
    <string name="pole_desc">Another technique with an erotic bias, but performed on a pylon (pole). The movements are dominated by sports acrobatics and choreography. All elements are performed slowly, smoothly and require considerable strength. Classes form a beautiful muscular relief, pump the whole body and develop endurance. The exercises are suitable for both women and men.</string>
    <string name="sheyping_title">Shaping</string>
    <string name="sheyping_desc">This type of exercise is nothing less than rhythmic gymnastics with a clear sequence of exercises. The workout includes different levels of programs based on scientific data for nine body types. Shaping is aimed at women between the ages of 30 and 50 and aims to reduce weight and volume, build a trim figure and generally strengthen the muscles of the body.</string>
    <string name="type_fintess_dr_title">Kinds of training</string>
    <string name="type_fintess_single_title">Kind of training</string>
    <string name="silovoy_training_title">Power Training</string>
    <string name="silovoy_training_desc">Strength training is the work with weights in the gym. The purpose of this training is to build muscle mass. The training consists of 30-40 minutes in anaerobic mode and 10-15 minutes in cardio zone. Each workout serves to work a particular muscle group, so you should work out at least three times a week to work the back, chest and legs separately. First you do 1-2 basic (multi-joint) exercises, they require more strength and energy. Then you work the same muscles, but with isolated exercises. The number of repetitions for men ranges from eight to 12 times, for girls from 12 to 20 times. Each exercise is done in four sets. The training ends with cardio exercises.</string>
    <string name="base_training_title">Basic Training</string>
    <string name="base_training_desc">This type of training is suitable for beginners who have to master the technique of performing exercises. Muscle groups are broken down by days of the week, e.g. on Monday you work the chest, on Wednesday the legs, and on Friday the back. In the beginning of the workout you do three basic exercises for the target group: four sets of 15 reps. The next workout is a circuit training for each muscle group except the one you worked in the beginning. The number of rounds is four, the number of reps for each exercise is 20 times. When the technique is built up, you can increase the intensity.</string>
    <string name="krug_training_title">Circle workout</string>
    <string name="krug_training_desc">Circle training is aimed at weight loss and is based on the use of strength exercises without rest. The circle includes one exercise for each muscle group. The number of laps depends on a person\'s training, the optimal number is from three to six. After each circle you rest. Before compiling a workout, it is necessary to decide which muscle groups you want to work, then certain exercises are used. The rest of the exercises are either not included in the training at all, or are done one at a time in a circle.</string>
    <string name="hit_training_title">HIIT training</string>
    <string name="hit_training_desc">This kind of training is considered high-intensity, so it is not suitable for everyone. You must not have any heart, joint or muscle diseases. The workout is based on an alternation of strength, static, and aerobic exercises. One round can include anywhere from four to an undetermined number of exercises that are performed without rest. During the workout, a high and moderate heart rate alternate, which has a positive effect on fat burning.</string>
    <string name="obem_training_title">Comprehensive training</string>
    <string name="obem_training_desc">This type of training is aimed at working on the forms. The training is suitable for those who do not want to lose or gain weight, but want to be toned. It is built like a strength training: basic and isolated exercises, but supersets and drop-sets are used, that is, for example, you do two exercises in a row without rest on the same muscle group. The repetition range for girls is 15 to 20 times, for men 12 to 15 times.  The load must be intense, that is, you should not just spin the exercise bike, and do it with acceleration, or using intervals, for example, 20 seconds at a moderate pace, 20 seconds of acceleration. At the same time, such a cardio workout should last at least 40 minutes.</string>
    <string name="exercise_dr_title">Exercises</string>
    <string name="exercise_single_title">Exercise</string>
    <string name="razvedenie_title">Dumbbell extension</string>
    <string name="razvedenie_desc">This arm exercise isolates the middle bundle of the deltoid muscles, visibly strengthening it and making it bulkier. By nature, the lateral parts of the shoulders are small, so their training should be approached carefully and dosed. The legs and back act as stabilizers, which receive additional load. Stand up straight and take dumbbells in your hands. The upper limbs should be slightly bent, thus avoiding excessive load on the elbow joints. Gently lift the dumbbells through the sides, feeling the tension in your shoulders. Lift strictly up to the T-shape pose. If you raise your arms above the parallel of the floor, you will engage the trapezoids, which is undesirable.</string>
    <string name="razgibanie_title">Arm extension</string>
    <string name="razgibanie_desc">This exercise for slender arms helps to isolate the load on the triceps, making the muscle stronger and stronger. The element also helps to get rid of the fat layer in the back of the arms, which is a pressing problem for many girls. The exercise is considered one of the most effective for working out triceps, be sure to include it in your arm workout at home.  Wrap both hands around the grip of the projectile, and then raise them above your head. Then lower the weight behind your head, bending your limbs to a right angle at the elbow. As you exhale, straighten your arms, lifting the dumbbell above you. Do not allow the elbow joint to close completely when straightening the arms to avoid excessive strain on it. Work at a moderate pace.</string>
    <string name="shim_title">Dumbbell Press</string>
    <string name="shim_desc">This arm exercise helps to actively load both the middle and anterior bundles of the shoulder muscles. The element is one of the most important in terms of strengthening the muscles of the upper extremities. With the help of the dumbbell press, every girl will be able to achieve a rounded and trim shape of the shoulders. Since the work takes place standing, legs and back play the role of stabilizers.  Taking the shells, lift them so that the forearms are perpendicular to the floor. Squeeze the weight over you with effort, while not allowing the elbow joint to latch completely. By following this rule, you reduce the risk of injury to your elbow. After that, slowly lower the weight into the starting phase and begin the next repetition.</string>
    <string name="low_planka_title">Low bar</string>
    <string name="low_planka_desc">Get into a supine position. Bend your arms at the elbows just under your shoulders and place your forearms on the floor. Extend your legs and place the pads of your feet on the floor. Lift your hips off the floor until your body is parallel to the floor and forms a straight line from your head to your feet. Keep your pelvis so that your back is straight. Do not allow your lower back (lumbar region) to sag or lift. Otherwise, the load on the back muscles will not be effective.</string>
    <string name="high_planka_title">High bar</string>
    <string name="high_planka_desc">The starting position is similar to the start for the low plank, but your arms should be kept straight and your body should be diagonal to the floor. Your body forms a straight line from your head to your feet.</string>
    <string name="most_title">The Bridge</string>
    <string name="most_desc">Lie on your back and put your head on the floor. Bend your knees so that your heels are directly under your knees. Keep your hands at your sides, palms down. Lift your pelvis so that your lower back stays straight. Point your shoulder blades inward and downward. Lift your hips up until they are completely straight and hold this position for 10 seconds while tensing the gluteal muscles. Then lower your hips and repeat the exercise. You may not touch the floor with your buttocks for extra exertion.</string>
    <string name="sport_library">Sports Library</string>
    <string name="text_nav">Change your life</string>
    <string name="all">All content</string>
    <string name="open_draw">Open</string>
    <string name="close_draw">Close</string>
</resources>